I know you don't care. You don't give a shit.
You look at that job you got.
We've had thieves here, and you're a thief.
Excuse me. Don't touch me.
No.
Don't touch me.
Excuse me.
Let me.
Excuse me. Please don't touch me.
Don't touch me.
If you...
You're literally touching me.
Don't get security.
Okay, yeah, do that, please, because she's...
Thank you. Please call security.
I'm on mute. I'm mute.
You don't get on mute.
Excuse me.
You don't...
You're...
Excuse me, ma'am.
Excuse me.
You're...
She's attacking me.
Please call security.
She's attacking...
You're attacking me.
Attacking me.
Please call security.
I'm calling you on mute.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Stop here.
Excuse me.
Hey, ma'am.
Amazon.
Do that, please.
Oh, please, please do it.
So this person is an Amazon delivery person.
The sister was delivering in an affluent apartment building in Houston.
She was wearing her Amazon vest.
She came in the building and was let into the building, into the elevator.
The lady who was accosting her told her that she needed to go to the concierge.
However, her delivery instructions said that she needed to leave it at the door,
and she decided to go with what the delivery instructions on the package said
versus listening to this random old white lady tell her what to do.
And that's when things went left.
Because I don't know if a lot of y'all want to admit this to yourselves,
but a lot of white people feel like they are the authoritarians over everybody.
And that if we do not do what they say, that we are all the terrible things that they say about us.
Hence why she felt completely fine in calling this person a thief, in accosting her.
Literally taking the package out of her hands and throwing it on the ground.
Thankfully, the delivery person has filed a police report,
but it hasn't gotten any response on the investigation.
So we need to continue to spread this video far and wide.
She's tagged here.
This is unacceptable.
Anti-Black racism is the plague and cancer of this world.
And I can promise you that were we to eradicate anti-Black racism,
90%, I'm going to be generous,
90% of the world's problems would actually be greatly diminished.
And if you scoffed at that assertion,
well, baby, I can explain it to you, but I can't make you understand it.
Ba-dum-bum!